The beginning of that
is the hardest part because let's be real,
when I started on
social media,
I was a very good personal trainer because
I just spent the last five
years just personal training.
Now I'm a very good content creator.
Do you know why?
Because I spent the last five years just
creating content.
You, where you are right now,
are an accumulation of everything you've
done in the
last three years. So if you're not
that great at running a business
or pumping out
content right now, for a lot of you,
I don't blame you because you should have
been
busy the last three years being a good
coach.
I'll teach you how to make better content
so you can get to that point that I
showed you on the board,
that you can quit your job
and you can go all in.
Then you can become a full-time content
creator that feeds that funnel.
And I'm not trying to say there's any
crazy maths here.
I've gone so pessimistic on each one.
Only 7,000 followers,
only 10% on the email list, only 1.5%
conversion rate, and that's a life
that you could rent an apartment,
get a good
MacBook, get a good camera,
have a good gym membership,
have a membership at a
local sauna and ice bath,
and still go out with your partner for two
meals a week